Nancy Monga

(Operations Assistant)

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am an enthusiastic, self-motivated, reliable, and hard working person. I am able to work well both in a team environment as well as using own initiative. I am able to work well under pressure. I have extensive experience in sales, both in B2B and B2C. In my previous roles, I was responsible for lead generation, building and managing client relationships, negotiating deals.

Currently, I am working with the responsibilities of an Operations manager where I have been responsible for overseeing the day-to-day operations of the company. This has included, implementing process improvements to increase efficiency. My sales experience has been valuable in this role, as it has given me a strong understanding of customer needs and how to deliver a high level of service.

EXPERIENCE

2022-09 - Operation Assitant 2023-07 -

- Ability to verify bills and invoices, ensuring accuracy and proper documentation.
- managing purchasing activities, including coordinating with vendors, comparing prices and evaluating options to make informed decisions that maximize cost savings.
- Experience in generating daily reports related to funds, analyzing financial data, and presenting it in a clear and concise manner.
- Understanding marketing objectives, comparing funds with other options, and preparing reports to support marketing decisions.
- Strong analytical skills to analyze financial and operational data, identify trends, and make data-driven recommendations.
- : Ability to cultivate and maintain positive relationships with partner companies, ensuring effective communication and collaboration.
- Proficiency in compiling relevant information and creating newsletters to update partner companies on news, developments, and updates.
- Excellent organizational skills to manage multiple tasks, prioritize responsibilities, and meet deadlines effectively.
- problem solving skills to address operational challenges, propose solutions, and implement improvements.
- Excellent verbal and written communication skills, build positive relationships.
- Efficiently managing time and resources to meet daily operational responsibilities and deliver tasks within designated timelines.
- Ability to adapt to changing priorities and work effectively in a dynamic environment.

2022-05 2022-09

Business Development Executive

• Piptan Association Pvt. Ltd., Ludhiana,

- · PB Defined and integrated roles,
- responsibilities and processes for business team and data management organization.
- Collaborated with sales and marketing departments to support project rollout.
- · Daily followups and aligning meetings for sales.

- 2021-09 -**Business Development Executive** 2022-04
 - Study Sid Pvt. Ltd., Mumbai, MH
 - Defined responsibilities and processes for business

team and data management organization.

- · Developed and executed strategic initiatives to implement key changes in B2C and improvements in business development and sales programs.
- Identified and pursued valuable business opportunities to generate IELTS counselings and enrollments for the same.
- 2021-07 -**Business Consultant** 2022-04
 - Pinkpearl (Coding Rig), Ludhiana, PB
 - Implemented process improvement to shape organizational culture in B2C, optimize procedures
 - for higher efficiency and help company evolve and grow.
 - Introduced new methods, practices and systems to reduce turnaround time.
 - Evaluated situations and delivered targeted
 - · solutions using various tools and resources.

EDUCATION

2016-12 -	Bachelor of ArtsEconomics	
2019-05	Punjab University - Chandigarh	
2020-09 - 2021-04	Diploma in Computer Application	
	Skill Tech Institute - Ludhiana	
2022-03	IELTS training	
2022-05	Mindway educational	

3	K	L	LS

MS Excel

Google Sheets

Sales pipeline management

Database Management

Tally Accounts

Calculating liabilities

MS Powerpoint

MS Word

CONTACT

Address Ludhiana, PB

Phone

+917710564314

E-mail

nancymonga576@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

Punjabi